electronictheatre.co.uk 2018-05-13

# Privacy Policy | Electronic Theatre

– Posted on 13 May, 2009 **Posted in:**[About Us](http://electronictheatre.co.uk/category/electronic-theatre-details/about-us)

Rating: 0.0/ **5** (0 votes cast)

 **Electronic Theatre** (together with its subsidiaries, “electronictheatre.co.uk” or “we”) has adopted a set of Privacy Principles applicable to all UK-based companies. **Electronic Theatre** has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use, and share personally identifiable information (information that can be used to identify you, such as your full name, email address, mailing address, or telephone number) (“PII”) we obtain from and about individuals located in the UK both online and offline.

**Electronic Theatre** is a general audience website, and does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age.

From time to time we may revise this Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our information collection and use practices, the features of **Electronic Theatre** , or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If we materially change our practices regarding use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.

#### Collection of PII by Electronic Theatre

**General**. **Electronic Theatre** collects PII in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in certain activities including (i) registration for certain online services and tools such as downloads, message boards, chat rooms or other community services; (ii) registration for special communications, such as email updates and newsletters; (iii) subscription registration; (iv) purchase products or services from or through **Electronic Theatre** ; (v) user surveys; (vi) events, sweepstakes, contests or promotions; and (vii) registration for online multi- or single-player gaming. We may obtain PII from third parties that we consider to be reputable. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in public areas of **Electronic Theatre** , such as the member home pages and forum, your information can be viewed and possibly used by others. We advise users to be especially careful in such public areas about disclosing PII, such as full name, home address, or phone number.

**Cookies**. Cookies are small bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit **Electronic Theatre**. We may use cookies to recognize users who have already registered, allowing those users to speed up their future activities. 

Third party advertisements displayed on **Electronic Theatre** may also contain cookies set by internet advertising companies or advertisers. **Electronic Theatre** does not control these cookies. You should check the privacy policy of the internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies.

You can set your computer to alert you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies, you may not have access to certain features on **Electronic Theatre**.

#### Electronic Theatre’s Use of PII

**Electronic Theatre** will use your PII in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. **Electronic Theatre** may use PII in aggregate, anonymous form for research purposes.

We may contact you regarding account status, changes to this Policy, our User Agreement or other terms of use, to confirm your registration, for customer service purposes or for any other business reason related to your use **Electronic Theatre**.

All of **Electronic Theatre** ’s policy is delivered in accordance with UK law. The collection of PII and the responsibilities of the authorities collecting such data may differ in countries not governed by UK law, for which **Electronic Theatre** cannot be accountable for.

### Related Posts:

  * No Related Posts

  *[Posted on 13 May, 2009]: 2009-05-13T12:34:41+01:00
